Li René Harmon

Twin Cities Area MN LinkedIn • Artstation

SUMMARY of QUALIFICATIONS

I am familiar with production hierarchies, tight deadlines, and long hours. I am comfortable working independently with minimal instruction while also remaining an enthusiastic team player doing my part to assure the project's timely completion. I am highly organized and detailed; I encourage team members; and I enjoy solving problems.

SKILLS and EXPERTISE

PC MAC UNIX MS Office	Digital Artist 3DS Max Maya Zbrush	3D Asset Creation 3D Environment Artist 3D Modeling & Textures Virtual Reality	Illustration Pencil, Pen & Ink Watercolour
Camtasia	Adobe Photoshop	•	Design and Layout
Desktop Support	Adobe Illustrator	Graphic Design	Research
Online Classes	Adobe Xd	User Interface Design	
	Adobe After Effects	User Experience	Leadership
HTML5	Adobe Animate	Information Architecture	Teaching
CSS3	Substance Suite	Wireframing	Curriculum Design
GitHub	Unity 3D	Creative Problem Solving	LMS
Typography	UE4	A/B testing	Remote teaching

EXPERIENCE

Atomikzen, Burnsville, MN	2000 – present	
Digital Artist		
Metcalf Middle School, Burnsville, MN	2019 – 2020	
Visual Art Teacher		
Art Institute, Las Vegas, NV	2013 - 2019	
Game Art Instructor - Fulltime		
Art Institute, Las Vegas, NV	2010 - 2012	
Academic Director / Instructor		
FIDM, Los Angeles, CA	2009 - 2010	
Interactive Media Instructor - Adjunct		
ITT Technical Institute, Sylmar, CA	2009 – 2010	
Game Art Instructor – Full Time		
Film Roman, North Hollywood, CA	2006 - 2008	
Digital Background Painter		
Painted backgrounds for the show The King of the Hill.		

ITT Technical Institute, Lathrop, CA 2003 – 2007

Game Art Instructor – Full Time

Fresno Art Museum, Fresno, CA 2003 - 2004

Coordinator of Media Art in Education

Created the Anime Club of Fresno

Yosemite High School, Oakhurst, CA 2000 - 2003

Interactive Media Instructor - Adjunct

Adviser to the Anime Club.

DreamWorks SKG, Glendale, CA 1998

Color Model / CG Artist

Color Model, Minor Effects and Rotoscoping for the movie *The Prince of Egypt.*

DiC Entertainment, Burbank, CA 1988 - 1997

Development Color Stylist

Supervised and trained color key artists for various shows including *The Real Ghostbusters, Street Sharks, Where in the World is Carmen San Diego, Extreme Dinosaurs* and *Captain Planet*.

Klasky Csupo, Hollywood, CA 1991

Color Supervisor

Headed the color department for the first Emmy Award-winning season of *Rugrats* Keyed Bart Simpson Butterfinger commercials.

PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT / EDUCATION

University of Minnesota, MN (2021)

Certificate in UX Design

Academy of Art University, CA (2021)

Masters of Fine Art. 3D

Modeling

National University, CA 2006

Masters of Science, Instructional Technology

Technology Development Center, CA 1999

Digital Animation,

Certificate

Gnomon, CA 1999

Alias Maya

Wavefront

California State University Northridge, CA 1990

Graduate Studies in Art

Education

Art Center College of Design, CA 1986

Bachelor of Fine Arts,

Illustration

Autodidact: 3DS Max; ZBrush; Photoshop; Substance Suite; Unity 5; Unity 3D; Unreal Engine; Marmoset; Illustrator; Premier; After Effects; Sound Forge; Xd; HTML; CSS;

DreamWeaver; Animo; UNIX (irix 6); Windows OS; Mac OS; PC; Virtual Reality; Augmented

Reality; Mixed Reality; HTC Vive; Oculus